Look here! If you don't
release my daughter and...
You are not in a position demand
anything or threaten us, Osman.
Osman, you had better listen to Commander Lucas.
After all, the one at the end of my dagger...
...is someone precious you wouldn't...
...want to lose.
A guest of Commander bucas...
...martyred both our spies and Baysungur.
I don't know her name.
No one knows her name.
All I know is it's a woman.
That woman..
The woman Ilbay mentioned.
Damn dogs!
Osman Bey.
What are we going to do now Osman Bey?
What do you want?
We will talk Osman.
We will talk.
Be patient Osman.
We will bargain for your loved ones.
Who are you?
Couldn't we find any trace of the
soldiers that were guarding Fatma?
Did they kidnap them too?
I don't know Holofira.
They are here.
They are here! They killed them.
They killed them
Gulce, Kismet.
Take their bodies secretly.
Take them to the tribe.
Fatma...
Oh Allah, protect Fatma.
Hazal Hatun, wait.
They are demons!
-They are demons!
-Hazal Hatun.
What are they doing to Saruca?
Oh Allah, they are so young.
Hazal Hatun!
Yusuf, Fatma
Hazal Hatun, be quiet.
We shouldn't let the people notice.
My heart is on fire.
How can I cope with it?
Hazal Hatun!
I understand your pain.
But if people hear that Osman
Bey's child is kidnapped...
...people could think that there
is weakness within the state.
Stay strong, please.
Sisters.
Take Hazal Hatun somewhere calm.
Come on.
Fatma, hold on my girl, nothing bad will happen.
Hold on.
Come closer Osman.
Come closer.
This might be the last
time you see your elaughter.
In any attempt...
...they will die.
Who are you?
She is the most ruthless
enemy of the Turks I know.
My good friend.
She is here to add her power to mine.
Also...
...I am the one...
...that sent you the box filled
with the fingers of your spies.
Dogs! Damn dastards!
So, you're the dastard I'm going to kill.
Take of your mask.
You can only see my face if you kill me.
When I take your corpse...
....and show it to the whole world...
...then everyone will'see your face.
Now tell me what you want.
What's the condition?
...want you to call off the siege.
Or your daughter Fatma and the young Beys...
...will die.
Father. Father!
I am willing to die here.
Don't you ever give up on the
conquest just to save me. Don't do it!
I'll die too Osman Bey!
I'll die too, my Bey!
Let's say I stopped the siege...
...will you give them to me?
Is this the only thing we'll
take from Osman, Lucas?
Of course not.
If I had a child...
...I'd give up the world for her.
Let's see, if Osman Bey...
...is willing to give up everything for her.
Karesioglu Beyhood
My Beys.
We have been patient....
...and tolerated Osman's uprisings.
We didn't want his soldiers to perish.
Yes, but now...
...all we saw in return were mistakes.
Let's punish him my Bey.
We will
We will.
A state doesn't get
power from its size.
The power comes from the
punishment it gives to rebels.
We'll make their heads bow...
...and knees fall to the ground.
This is my order!
My army will be ready.
Now it's time for war.
As you wish my Bey.
May I come in my Bey?
Come in Sancar.
Lucas and the Hatun.
They took Osman Bey's girl Fatma Hatun.
Beys wait for my command.
You may leave now.
Sancar.
What are you saying?
How did it happen?
They say the Hatun with Lucas did it.
She took Fatma Hatun,
Begum Hatun's brother Yusuf...
...and Bayhan Bey's son Saruca.
Is that so?
The Hatun's a sneaky one.
Whoever the Hatun is, she
beat Osman Bey without a fight.
Osman.
Your arrogance caused this.
If he'd listened to me...
...now I'd be with Osman, Sancar.
I'd do something about Lucas' game.
What will you do now my Bey?
You must avoid interacting with a wolf.
But if you have to, you must not
leave it just injured.
An injured wolf would come back to kill, Sancar.
Now it's time to take out the wolf.
Time to take out Osman.
I think Lucas is right Osman.
He's right.
You're a father who'd give
up the world for her daughter.
What's your condition?
What is it?
Lifting the siege is enough
for you to have the Beys but...
Your daughter, Fatma...
She is a piece of your heart, Osman.
For her...
Would you give a piece of your nation's heart...
...Sogut...
Can you give up on it for her?
Who are you? Who are you to
ask for a piece of my nation's land.
You lowlife dogs.
Do you see it Lucas?
He got so mad.
Father.
Don't yield to these devils, don't.
Your daughter is running towards
death, Osman. Don't listen to her.
You will clear Sogut of
your soldiers and folk...
...and surrender it to us.
Your people...
You will get them at the city square tomorrow.
You lowlife dog...
You'll pay for this.
We would've loved to stay here...
...and listen to you Osman...
...but we're very busy.
Don't forget it.
Tomorrow.
At the Sogut city square.
Don't forget.
You lowlife...
I'll have the upper hand on you one day.
Fatma.
You will regret this.
Daughter...
Mother.
You lowlives...
Let me go.
I've told you Lucas.
I've told you that I will
sever Osman's lifeline.
He's just losing blood for
now but when he loses Sogut...
...then he'll be destroyed completely.
Devil.
Devil, do you think Osman bey
will let you get away with this?
Let me go.
Let go.
You'll die.
Let go. Let him go. Let go.
Your life depends on what
comes out of our mouths.
Where is Osman Bey now? Where is he?
Whose feet are you under?
Let go.
Let go. Don't do it.
-Know your limits, you dog!
-Let go. Let him go.
Let go.
You're not the son of a bey anymore.
Right now, you're just a captive.
Soldiers! Take him to the dungeon
Don't... touch... her..
Stop!
Don't take the girl
I have better plans for her.
Do you think Osman is going to give
up on Sogut in return of his daughter?
It is Kayi's most precious land.
He has no other option but it
won't be in return of his daughter.
He will never get
his daughter from me!
Come on, brother!
Drink. Drink. It's quite chilly.
You'll feel much better, my brothers!
Osman.
Osman, stop.
My Osman.
Stop, my Bey! Stop
My Bey, stop
How can I stop?
How can I stop, my Bala, huh?
I left my daughter Fatma
in that infidel's hands.
How can I wait?
My Bey.
-I can't control my anger.
-My Bey.
No, I want to
destroy that castle!
I want to burn it to the ground!
My Bey, you are wounded.
We need to stop the bleeding.
Bala, stop.
I don't care about my wound
My daughter is there!
If they touch my daughter, if they harm her...
...I will leave none of them alive!
I will cut them into pieces!
That's all I know!
Are we going to give Sogut to them?
My Fatma on one hand.
My blue eyed darling girl.
And on the other hand...
...the lands we established our state, Sogut.
Both of them...
...are entrusted to me by great Allah.
What will we do?
Our daughter is in that woman's hands.
What are we going to do?
Who is that demon?
Who is that damned woman?
How could she kidnap our sister?
First our spies...
...then Baysungur.
Now...
...now my sister Fatma!
Whoever that demon is, she knows us well.
Brother...
...who is this person that
holds a grudge against us?
How could she dare to
kidnap our beloved sister!?
My shahzade, they can't
do anything to Fatma Hatun.
Don't worry.
We will go and take her, with the help of Allah.
They can't harm her. If they harm her...
...they know that we would
burn down the whole world.
But we need to make a move.
We will make a move, Aykurt.
Send a pigeon to Ilbay.
We will need him.
As you command my Shahzade.
Alaeddin.
Look at me.
It's not the time to be sad or to grieve.
It's time to stand tall and take action.
We will! We will.
We will show them what it means to hurt us!
All of them!
We will, with the help of Allah.
Let go of me! You dastards!
-Act like a man! - If you...
If Fatma Hatun gets hurt...
...I'll make this castle your grave
Dastards!
You damned idiots!
Dogs
Be a man!
Yusuf.
You're strong...
...and I'm smart.
Come on.
Let's work together.
Two Beys from enemy tribes...
...can burn this castle to the ground.
You're a child living in the
shadow of your father, Saruca Bey.
We can't work together.
But if fate wants two enemies to work together..
...then we'll do it.
We'll work together for Fatma Hatun.
We'll save her from here...
...and send these dastards to hell.
Alright.
Now let's think about how to escape...
...from this cell.
Osman Bey's Base.
What did we do?
How did we leave our
children there and come back?
They want Sogut in return for their lives.
What will we do now?
I don't trust that soulless woman's words.
Even if we do as they say,
their lives are in danger.
Hold on. Get it together all of you.
Infidels have our children.
We can't sit here think bad thoughts.
No. We will not fall down.
Now...
...we must talk about how
to bring back our children.
Tell me.
Bayhan Bey.
How do we get them back...
...without losing anyone?
Begum Hatun's right, my Bey.
Even if we do as they say...
...we don't know if we can save our children.
We need to find another way.
There may be a secret
passage leading to the castle.
Can we save them from there...
...without risking them getting hurt Bayhan Bey?
Tell me Begum Hatun.
What should we do?
We shouldn't have lifted the siege my Bey.
Then they would have known...
...we'd attack the castle
if the prisoners are hurt.
While they fought off the siege...
...we'd have done it.
If we had kept the siege...
...they could have killed Yusuf
and Sarucan, and kept Fatma alive.
We aim to save all three of them.
Gencer Bey.
Tell us what we must do.
My bey...
...I say...
...since he's working with those
lowlives and gets along with them...
...then let's go and talk with Karesi Bey.
Let's use him as the middleman.
What are you saying Gencer Bey?
You both say that Karesi Bey works with them...
...and say we should trust Karesi
Bey with those so dear to us, is that so?
I've listened to you all.
I've made my decision.
It's my order.
We're going to empty the city.
We will evacuate the people
and the alps from Sogut.
Osman must be going crazy with
desperation and anger right now.
But he definitely will try
to trick us to save Sogut.
I'm sure of that.
But we won't let him get the chance.
Those stupid boys...Saruca and Yusuf.
One of them is the brother of Begum
Hatun, and the other the son of Bayhan Bey.
While we have both of their most
loved ones here, in our dungeons...
...we can get Osman's secret plan from them.
Good.
Let's get going right away.
Bayhan will talk right
away to save his only son.
He's greedy.
He will betray Osman for
his own benefit right away.
You said Begum Hatun and
Karesi Bey meet up frequently.
When her loyalty for Osman is this fragile...
...why wouldn't she betray him for her brother?
We'll use them both Sofia.
Both of them.
They will give us all
the information we want
about Osman while we
have their loved ones here.
They both must be with Osman right now.
They must be planning at
their headquarters in Akhisar.
Send word right away.
Come with me.
Your meal is ready, ma'am.
Fatma?
She's waiting for you.
They told us to lift the siege and we did.
That's okay. But...
...giving them Sogut...That's
not possible my bey.
Gencer Bey...
How will we control those
who swore loyalty to us if we...
...give the capital of the
nation to the infidels, my bey?
Let's fight. I'll give my life at the
front of the line for our kids but...
...this won't do, it's
against the tradition my bey.
Hold on.
Hold on Gencer Bey.
I've told you...
...to show us a way out. But what did you do?
You talk about Karesi
who works with the infidels.
Like that wasn't enough,
you speak against my word.
My bey...
Enough Gencer Bey, enough.
You continue to defend Mekece.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
What I'm going to say...
..is a secret.
We will take the people
and the alps out of Sogut.
We will evacuate the city.
When that demon woman and Lukas...
...comes the city, the
only thing they will find...
...will be their death.
How is it going to happen, my Bey?
It will happen.
And it will happen in a surprising way.
The enemy came right into our face...
...came inside...
...kidnapped Fatma Hatun from the bazaar...
...killed the sisters, shed our blood...
...and you!
What were you doing, Alps?
Look at my face
Huh?
What were you doing?
Were you sleeping?
Alps were watching everywhere
but we couldn't realize.
You should have realized it!
You should have seen it! You
should have spotted it, Alps!
Go back to your duty, Alps!
Keep your eyes peeled
When the time comes...
...everyone of you will be punished!
But now the bazaar needs
to be protected more than ever.
Right now, Alps!
What do you think you are doing, huh?
You can't even control
the hatuns in your stall...
...but you act as if you were me and
dare to speak after my words, Holofira?
Keep it together, Gonca.
Is it time to be divided? The enemy
infiltrated among us. They took Fatma.
What could we get
by scorning the Alps?
And we should get back to
the tribe as soon as possible.
No.
I know your intention very well, Holofira.
Tell me what my intention is then.
What could my intention be, when
Fatma is in the enemies hands?
Tell me.
Gonca Hatun!
We are ready to set out.
When the time comes...
...everyone's intention
will be revealed, Holofira.
As we spoke, I sent word to our future spies.
Come on, let s have a nice meal.
Do you think I would sit on the
same table as dastards like you?
Sit together with us?
No. You are not here to join us...
..but to serve us.
You Turks would make great servants.
We Turks were not born to be servants...
...nor prisoners!
We were born to be the
executioner of oppressors like you!
Your ancestors know that best!
We will celebrate our victory.
Bring alcohol.
She will serve.
Come on, bring our drinks.
Do as she says!
If you are thirsty...
..you can take a sip.
I could kill you right here!
But I need you alive for a while.
Kill me right now as you have chance!
Or you will regret it terribly!
Are you also bored, Lucas?
Let go!
Take her to the dungeons.
Let go of me!
Yusuf.
Stop that.
It won't open.
At least I'm trying. What are you doing?
We don't know if Fatma Hatun is okay or not.
I'll go crazy if I don't get out.
Tell us is Fatma Hatun okay?
Say something dastards! Is she alright?
-I have a plan.
-What?
I got it.
Hold it. Come on.
Come on.
What is it Saruca?
My stomach
Saruca what is it?
Yusuf, it worked for my mother before.
When the soldiers come in
to check on me, we'll attack.
Is that it?
Come on
Soldiers!
Call a healer!
Ilbay.
You'll enter Akhisar Castle.
It won't be easy this time my Bey.
But I'll sneak in for you.
We trust you Ilbay.
You've never failed us until now...
...but this time our children are at risk.
A single mistake...
I'll show them the strength of Kayi Bala Hatun.
Don't you worry.
Get prepared for when you get inside.
Orhan and Alaeddin will come
tomorrow to save Fatma and other Beys.
Alaeddin.
They bring fresh grass for
the horses in Akhisar Castle.
You'll add this to the grass.
Horses will get sick from it.
No.
These are poisonous.
Don't touch them with your bare hands.
Be careful.
Then what do I do?
Then it's the important part.
No one will make a mistake.
Otherwise...
...we'll pay for it with the children's lives.
Now listen closely.
He's in pain.
Let me go!
Walk! Walk!
What's going on here?
Fatma Hatun?
Are you okay?
Fatma Hatun
I'm dying.
What's wrong with Saruca?
He's almost dead.
Take him to a healer. He's the son of a Bey.
Lucas will make you pay for it if he dies.
Come on now!
Come on. Call a healer! Help
him! Don't just stand there.
My stomach
Walk! We're going to see a healer!
Come on.
Stand back! Stand back!
Come on!
Fatma Hatun.
Fatma Hatun
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Did that red witch hurt you?
No, she can't do anything to me. Come on.
Come on we're going
to get out of here and ruin
their plans. Come on,
let go of the captives.
Get the swords, brother.
-Come on.
-Save the others.
Saruca, get the swords.
Come on.
The army is withdrawing to the tribe.
Come on, if we're done
let's get moving, come on.
As you wish my bey.
Come on alps.
Begum Hatun.
We're going to save them, you know that right?
I do.
I do Bayhan Bey.
But for the first time, I'm feeling this scared.
Yusuf...
My brother...
Lhave to take care of him.
If something happens to him..
It won't.
We've been enemies for years.
I would've never thought
that we'd be on the same side.
But...
...it's Allah's will.
Now...
...we'll unite...
..and save our loved ones.
God willing.
If you want your son to live...
If you want Yusuf to live
come to the tavern tonight.
Come to the tavern tonight
without telling anyone anything.
Alone.
Let's get out of here before
the soldiers come. Come on.
Come on.
They're escaping.
-Come on.
Fatma Hatun.
Dead or alive...
You can't escape this hell
without me allowing you.
This hell will be your
grave, you snake.
You Turkish scums.
Do you have these brave
words cursing through your blood?
I can smell the fear you feel deep inside.
From the babes in their cradles...
...to the sisters that are
swinging their swords...
None of the Turks have even a shadow of fear.
You lowlife...
Is that so?
Let's see. Soldiers, don't get involved.
Come.
My sword will be dirtied with your blood.
Is that all you got?
Osman's daughter...
Enough.
Let her go. Fight me you lowlife.
That's enough entertainment.
Don't touch Fatma Hatun.
Don't.
Soldiers, throw them in the dungeon.
Host them well.
Don't let them die but rip out that strange...
...braveness...
..in their heart.
Let go.
Your end will come.
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you.
What is up? What brings you here?
You are my elder, Karasi Bey.
I came to ask mercy.
If the young knows who his elder is, he
becomes a greater man than his elder.
Tell me. What is the problem?
Osman Bey, my Bey.
He's like a shooting arrow without a target.
He wants to give Sogut to the enemy
because they kidnapped Fatma Hatun.
Unspeakable!
Unseen!
A Turk surrenders his land to the
infidels without using his sword, huh?
We are Beys knowing our customs, my Bey.
We don't disobey our Bey but you
should interfere as our elder, my Bey!
This makes my blood boil!
It won't only make your blood boil.
If it keeps going like this, it will cause
your blood to be shed, Gencer Bey.
If Osman keeps going
like this, he will cause
everyone's end around
him just as he did to himself.
You did the right thing by coming to me.
Don't you worry. I'll go to
Osman and have a word with him.
I'll show him the right way.
You are great, Karasi Bey.
-Thank you.
-Thnka you.
The first leaf has fallen, Sancar.
Osman's plane tree has
started to experience the autumn.
Its fall is imminent.
Come on!
We are going to save Fatma Hatun.
Come on, Ayse! Take your sword.
I got it.
Don't waste your breath. My
father will save Fatma Hatun.
Your father is a stableman!
How is he going to save Fatma
Hatun? And we should go there, too!
Oh but...
...if you are scared, do not come!
Firstly, nothing can scare me!
Secondly, my father is much more than you think!
Your father is a stableman! How can he be more?
My father is a Bey! A Bey!
He has also double sword!
Your father is a stableman!
You know nothing! My
father is not only a stableman!
What is the thing I
don't know? Then, tell me
and let me know what
your father's importance is!
I'll make you regret for what you
said! You'll see who my father is now!
Look at this! My father!
You!
-What were you doing with things in your hands?
Mother! We are going to save Fatma Hatun!
We are going to save Fatma
Hatun! Give me my sword!
You will harm yourselves, kids.
Gazi, don't make me mad or I'll beat you!
Try touching them again
Gonca Hatun!
Tell her something. I can't sit idly.
Gazi, stop. Stop. Your mother is right.
We can do nothing but pray.
Holofira Hatun, if my father
learns I got it, he will get mad.
Let me put it back.
Okay.
Okay, but let's do it together, okay?
I wouldn't want you to get hurt.
Okay then, I'll show you the place.
Okay, come on.
My Bey.
As you commanded, we are gathering the people.
The people will be sad when they
hear that the city will be emptied.
And some will object it.
The people will be convince.
I am doing this for their future.
I can't bring them into this war.
But...
-This time it's different.
-Don't!
We will stand tall and never fall into despair.
We will not give the infidels what they want.
The infidels may have treacherous tactics...
...but we have the swords of The Righteousç
As long as we never stray
from the path of the Righteous...
...we won't be defeated even
the whole world comes after us.
Thank Allah.
We have enough lands to bury them all.
Orhan, Alaeddin.
Now...
...you will tell the people this.
This...
...duty is yours.
-As you command my Bey.
Kayi Tribe.
The kids aren't here.
Bayhan Bey.
Where is Saruca?
Why didn't you bring my son?
I will explain, hatun.
Why are you alone? Where
are Osman Bey and Mother Bala?
Is Fatma okay?
Tell me you found them, Begum Hatun.
They are asking for Sogut
in exchange of our kids.
Until then, they are prisoners
of the infidels in Akhisar.
Oh Allah, protect them.
Allah! Allah!
Stand strong, hatun.
Saruca.
People!
Sisters!
Brothers!
We've been through bad days...
...and good days, up until today.
There were times...
...we cried and we laughed.
Now I say to you...
...our state is in hardship.
The infidels...
...have our sister Fatma...
...and my Bey's sons.
Allah damn them! Dastards! Killers!
We won't let the get away!
Infidels want something from us.
It will be hard for you.
We know it.
Our decision will hurt you.
It will, but...
But...
...to save our sister Fatma...
..we must do this.
Our land Sogut...
...will be given to Byzantine.
What would we do my Bey? Where will we go?
Isn't there another way?
How can we give up our land for this, Beys?
If there was another way...
...we'd have found it.
But there isn't.
We'll get through this.
Don't worry.
Our tribe will welcome you all.
Don't think we'll kneel before them.
Don't think we'll bow our heads before them.
They cut our beard today.
But I swear to you...
...we'll cut out their hearts...
...like they cut off our beard.
Don't you worry.
Very soon..
...you will be back here.
But...
...those who did this to my people...
...will pay for it.
As Osman Bey, I swear to it.
Peace be with you stableman.
I'm a foreigner.
I want to go to Bursa.
Where should I be heading?
Go towards the sunrise.
You'll find the path.
Thank you, stableman.
Come on.
Go on stableman.
You'll open the gates to the castle for us.
Fatma...
How is she right now?
Do you think she's scared?
Our Fatma wouldn't be scared.
She wouldn't be.
Everyone knows about Sogut.
Holofira, Gonca.
Tell me, how are the people?
Not good, father.
They blame you.
If they knew that you weren't
going to give them Sogut...
Let them blame me for now.
Let them.
But don't forget this.
One person.
Even if one person makes a mistake...
...Fatma and the kids will be in danger.
May Allah forbid.
Lucas...
...and that devil beside him...
They both want to make the
people lose their trust in us.
But they won't be successful.
We're going to get Fatma...
...and Sogut both.
Then...
Then people will understand.
The anger will die down then.
What if they realize our plan, father?
No.
They won't realize it.
We prepared.
With Allah's permission, we will be successful.
-God willing.
Orhan, Alaeddin.
You are to leave the tribe before sunrise.
But...
...don't be seen by anyone.
I don't trust that lowlife Lucas at all.
As you wish father.
As you wish my bey.
Osman
I didn't want them to know but...
...what if they realize our plan?
What will we do then?
We made our plan.
We'll wait now.
Lucas.
Are you going to see which
fish we caught with our net?
You're right Sofia.
Today, Bayhan or Begum...
One of them will be caught by our net.
And they will tell us the plans
Osman made one by one.
Even if they help us...
...both Bayhan and Begum's end
is the same as Osman's, Lucas.
Them, their kids...
...all the Turks...
They will taste death by our hands.
All of them, Sofia.
All of them.
They will lose Sogut first...
...then their lives.
Yes.
Sarucan..
My son..
Son..
Please, bey...
...don't let anything happen to my son.
Please, I'm begging you.
Don't let anything happen to him.
Be strong, hatun.
I understand. It's the heart of a mother.
We'll take him back, hatun. We'll take him back.
How can we trust the infidels, my Bey?
Now...
Who knows what they are doing to my son?
My dear son! My dear son!
My son was taken with a broken heart.
Did he throw himself to the fire
just to prove his worth to you?
Saruca! Saruca!
If you want your son to be alive, come to
the inn without saying anything to anyone.
Alone.
Where are you going, my Bey?
We'll save him.
Wipe away your tears now.
I'll bring him to you one way or another.
Be careful, my Bey.
My Allah! My Allah! Help me!
Protect our children!
Brother.
My mother's...
...and my father's legacy.
I was not only a sister...
...but I was also your mother.
I can't leave you there.
You are left to me from my father.
Leave them! It's enough! Leave them
-Leave them alone!
-We have just started.
Enough! Enough
The price of trying to escape
from my dungeon is heavy.
Leave them! Leave them!
They are the sons of Beys!
Osman Bey will make you
pay for this! He'll make you pay!
The Beyhood is over!
The punishment is over!
There is only torture from now on!
If you don't want to
experience the same thing...
...shut your mouth up.
You have only power over our bodies!
But against our cause you have no power!
When you face Osman Bey...
...what will you do, huh? What will you do?
I pity you so much! So much
-Fatma!
-Fatma Hatun!
Don't touch her! Don't touch her, you rat!
I can crush you like a bug! I can destroy you.
But look! I'm waiting, huh? I'm waiting.
When we take Sogut
tomorrow, I'll also take your life.
Do you understand?
What's going on?
Ma'am, all the horses in the castle
got sick. I guess there is a outbreak.
Then, what are you waiting for?
Bring new horses immediately!
You, cursed ones!
I'll settle the accounts with you tomorrow!
You dog
Welcome.
Bayhan Bey.
It's because we can speak freely.
Where is my son?
Where is Saruca?
He's in good hands.
You told me you were going to give me
my son, when I told you Osman Bey's plan.
That was our deal.
I'll keep my promise.
But if I gave your son right now...
...your treachery would be
revealed quickly, Bayhan Bey.
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow, you'll get your son.
Commander!
I swear on the Holy Bible that nothing
will happen to your son, Bayhan Bey.
You'll take your son back safe and sound.
What about the others?
The others...
Unfortunately, Begum Hatun
wasn't clever as you were.
I also sent her words but she didn't respond.
You were the only clever
one who accepted my offer.
Who can say anything to a
father, who betray his Bey...
...for his son's life?
Now...
I listen to you.
What is Osman's plan?
Osman Bey has evacuated Sogut.
He's going to plant gunpowder
in the every corner of Sogut.
When you come inside,
there will be a big explosion.
That's how he plans to kill you.
You think you are so clever, huh, Osman?
I should have guessed it.
Lukas.
You promised me. You were going to
give my son, when I revealed the secret.
I'll keep my promise, Bayhan Bey.
Goodbye.
Peace and mercy of Allah be upon you.
Oh Allah.
You are the Greatest.
I take shelter in your mercy.
Don't test me with the
pain of losing my brother.
Please bring him back to me.
Fatma.
Welcome father.
Thank you.
Thanks.
I had a table prepared for you.
And I cooked half of the meals.
What did you prepare for your father?
I prepared meat.
And I made kavut as a dessert.
Praise be!
I also cooked Komec.
I like it. My dear.
Thank you.
Fatma..
Oh my blue eyed darling girl.
Fatma.
What if something happened to you?
What if I couldn't see you again?
What would I do then?
Well, you don't see us,
Osman Bey! You see your alps.
You see Iltutan.
You even see your enemies more than us!
You either go to battle,
or get ready for battle.
Do you have to be Osman Bey all
the time? When will you be our father?
Come here.
My Fatma.
When necessary, I am Osman Bey.
When necessary, I am your father.
I want to see my father more.
My dear.
Oh Allah.
You are the One who protected
Hadrath Ibrahim from fire.
The One who protected
Hadrath Nuh from the storm.
Oh Allah.
Just as You protected...
...Hadrath Yunus' inside
the belly of the fish...
...protect my daughter.
Protect her oh Allah.
My daughter on one hand.
And my land is on the other.
I won't give either of them
Oh Allah, give me strength.
Give me power, oh Allah.
Give me power.
Ameen, Osman.
Ameen.
I know your heart is on fire.
You are hiding it, but I can see it.
I recognize the pain, because I have the same.
I won't hide it, Osman.
I am scared.
Allah knows...
...we were tested with our child before.
But it's different.
I swear to you Bala.
The infidels...
...try to hurt our children.
They try to hurt us.
No.
I never bowed down to anyone.
Anyone.
Fatma won't do it either.
She's her father's girl.
She's strong.
She is.
She is strong.
They live for the state...
...the state lives for them.
Fatma knows it well.
She won't bow down.
Never.
She won't Osman.
She won't.
Allah.
You're Strong enough for all.
Give us strength.
Don't make me bow down.
Don't test my mother...
...and my father...
...with this pain.
They can't handle it again.
Ameen.
I heard your your sister died.
It happened long ago.
How did it happen?
None of your business.
Don't you dare speak of my sister.
I don't even remember her name.
Poor thing.
Did you miss her?
Soon.
Soon you'll be with her.
Is that okay?
Then your brothers will join.
You can never hurt them.
Then Bala...
And of course...
I'll kill your father too.
No. You can't touch them.
You're not strong enough.
Allah is with us.
We'll leave with Alaeddin and the Alps at dawn.
Fatma..
...my sister will be saved, God willing.
But the infidels...
They won't be able to get away from us.
I'll do anything to kill
them. I'll risk my life.
I'm ready to do whatever I can for Fatma.
I'll give my life for her too.
But when it's about your life...
...I get so scared.
My sweet Orhan.
Let this protect you, okay?
Let this give you strength.
Holofira..
My kind hearted one...
My beautiful faced one.
Of course.
But tell me...
...where did this
Jawshan Kabir come from?
At the bazaar.
When I heard about Fatma..
We need to go to the tribe.
They must've heard about Fatma.
We need to reassure the people.
I'll talk with the women here.
Begum Hatun isn't here either.
They'll take care of the bazaar.
Okay.
Come on Gulce.
God...
...protect them.
Show mercy to them.
It felt like my heart was
being crushed by a mountain.
A random aunt...
She gifted this to me.
You're Osman Bey's daughter in law right?
Your heart feels heavy, right girl?
Do you have a problem or...
I got some bad news.
Your heart feels like it was set aflame.
Let this be a gift from me.
It's a Jawshan.
May Allah protect you from all kinds of evil.
When I held it, it felt like
the pressure I felt lightened.
I said, okay nothing will happen to Fatma.
God willing.
Let this protect you too.
So that woman helped you
just like Hadrath Hizir huh?
Hizir?
Who is he?
Hadrath Hizir...
...is the one that accompanied
Hadrath Musa in Al-Kahf.
The one who rushes to help the ones in need.
Holofira.
Once we save Fatma...
Once we get rid of these troubles...
...do you want me to read
you the Al-Kahf to you?
You can learn who he is from the verses.
Will you really?
Of course.
Yes. I'd love that.
Holofira..
Bayhan betrayed Osman for his son.
Good.
Good job Bayhan.
Where did you come from?
From the dungeons.
She never gives up right? That little devil...
She's stubborn just like her father.
I'm more stubborn than them, Lucas.
If you know your enemy well...
...you'll always start the
fight one step ahead of them.
I know how to hurt them,
how to break their will so well.
Now.
What did Bayhan say? What is Osman's plan?
Tell me.
Bayhan...
There's a letter from your daughter Poena.
Do you have a daughter Sofia?
Poena.
My little brutal angel.
How can you keep this from me?
There's still a lot of things you
have to learn about me, Lucas.
Poena.
So, I have a niece.
What does she say? Is she coming here?
Impatient little devil...
She's asking for permission to come to me but...
...not now.
When the time comes, I'll bring her here.
Poena.
What's its meaning?
The punisher...
...of the Goddess of Punishment, Nemesis.
Revenge, the soul of pain.
Poena.
Why do you put such a name, Sofia?
I'll tell you later.
Now...
You tell me the things you learned from Bayhan.
Fatma! Daughter! Say something
I'm here, daughter! I'm here
Fatma! I'm here! I'm here, daughter.
I'll save you.
Fatma
What is this?
How can it be?
Why are they here?
Who hung these? Where is the flag of Kayi?
Don't do it! I beg you!
We are divided!
Our state has fallen!
Osman Bey lost Sogut!
Where can we go now?
No. No.
We lost nothing.
Sogut still belongs to us.
Our state stays strong
Sogut is gone!
Who says this?
Fatma?
My Fatma
Daughter! I'm here!
My blue-eyed daughter! My beautiful daughter!
Don't be afraid. No one can
hurt you. You are safe now.
Come here. Come here.
What are you doing here?
You, dastard! What
are you doing here?
Don't you dare touch my daughter!
You are late, Osman.
You lost Sogut.
Don't you dare to
touch Fatma! I'll kill you
And it's time for...
...your daughter, Fatma.
I'll kill you! I'll kill you now!
Don't do it, Fatma.
Don't do it, daughter.
Don't touch her!
-I am her executioner.
-You dog!
Father.
No! My Allah!
No.
No!
Fatma
Osman.
Oh Allah.
Oh Allah, give me strength to
save my daughter from them.
Grant me power and patience.
Ameen.
We will wake up to a better morning, Osman.
God willing.
The pain in our hearts will go away, God willing.
God willing. God willing.
Kayi Tribe
Alaeddin.
I should come with you.
It's hard to sit and wait.
No.
You'll protect the tribe.
Don't worry sweetheart.
We'll save my sister.
We will.
Your love for Fatma is different Alaeddin.
My sister...
When we lost Halime so young..
...I devoted myself to Fatma so much.
She healed our never healing wounds.
From that day on, I never left her side.
My beautiful sister...
My dear sister...
A sibling is something else Alaeddin.
Their absence creates a hole in your heart.
It's impossible to fill.
But...
...you will reunite with your sister.
God willing.
God willing, we will save Fatma.
Alaeddin.
Brother.
Come on brother, it's time.
Let's go and save our sister.
Let's go and bring her back home.
Yes.
There is no joy in the tribe without her.
Right.
Come on.
May Allah protect you.
You too.
Safe travels.
Bala, we will go and get our daughter back.
Fatma will prepare dinner tonight,
and tease her brothers again.
She will hide behind us.
She will come.
She will.
We will ruin their traps!
Our sons will get Fatma back.
And we will go for Sogut.
Can I come in my Bey?
Come in, Turahan.
My Bey. Karesi Bey is coming.
Call the Beys.
As you command, my Bey.
Osman...
You will make the decision.
You will either listen to me, or...
...these people who are in despair
and ashamed of what you are doing...
...will come to me for hope.
Bayhan Bey's blindness will be your end, Osman.
It will be a pity
for his big plan.
They're ready to replace
the prisoners as you wish.
Good.
Fatma will stay in the dungeon.
Don't even give water to those idiots.
So they'll learn their lesson.
Prepare the horses.
Today...
Today will be our biggest victory, Sofia.
We'll take Sogut from Osman.
Akhisar Castle
Wait.
Where are you coming from?
From Bursa.
Akhisar's horses are ill.
I was ordered to bring horses.
I took care of them well.
They'll help the Akhisar soldiers.
That's enough. I know about this.
You shall pass.
Open the gates.
I told you not to do it.
I told you not to go into
Akhisar but you never listened.
Now, everyone knows
that those who don't listen...
...will fail and lose their power.
In return for your child's life...
...infidels wanted...
...Sogut, the heart of your state.
Now,
what I am saying is...
Cut it short Karesibey.
To give up Sogut, a Turk's land to infidels...
...is the biggest ignorance.
Come...
...and announce you and
your Beys are under my rule....
...so that I can help
you with all of my power.
You can both keep Sogut...
...and save your children's lives.
You are...
...a Bey who has worked with many infidels.
Why would I side with you?
Yes.
Do you see now which one of us...
...doesn't want to unite?
To unite...
You're right.
You said if you go to Akhisar...
...we'd be enemies.
And without thinking, you said...
...'I have Akhisar now'...
...'and I'll deal with you later.'
That's it.
I still keep my word Karesi Bey.
You're going after battles you can't win.
...and those who follow you will be
defeated in the battles you'll participate.
Karesi Bey.
Me and the men who follow me...
...are enough to take you out.
Don't you worry.
Karesi Bey.
The castle gates are opening.
The prisoners' faces are covered.
How will we know?
As we thought, Alaeddin.
That's not Fatma.
How did you know my Shahzade?
We're siblings, Boran Bey.
Our father trained us a lot.
If that was our Fatma...
...she would've heard us
and let us know that's her.
Hold on sister.
Hold on.
Your brothers will come and get you.
Come on.
Water...
Give us water...
He's asking for water. Don't
you hear him? Give him water.
Saruca
Hold on.
Hold on Saruca.
It's all my fault.
That devil wanted me.
You're not guilty.
Don't be sad.
Let's think of it like we're fasting.
Fatma Hatun.
Don't mind Saruca, Fatma Hatun.
He's a bit fussy, he's a mama's boy after all.
Is this coming from Yusuf Bey
who is living under his sister's shadow?
Now...
Now, the enemy will have Sogut as well...
Who knows what else that devil asked for...
We have to get you out of here
before that devil is here, but how?
We'll find a way.
We will.
I've brought food for the captives.
I wished they died from starvation but...
...commander Lucas doesn't want them to die.
Give those to us, we'll give them the food.
No one else will go in there but us.
You're tired.
I'll take care of it.
You go, we'll do it.
Water.
So you wanted water...
Here you go, water.
Lowlife.
Ilbay?
That's Ilbay, thank Allah. Thank Allah.
Fatma Hatun.
-Ilbay.
-Brother, Ilbay.
Thank you brother.
Make haste.
How did you get in Ilbay?
We don't have time, Fatma Hatun.
Wear these and let's get out of here.
Come on.
Hey people!
My Beys.
My sisters. My brothers.
Now...
Everywhere you'll settle is ready.
Everywhere is prepared.
Everything you'll need we'll be there.
But I know.
You feel pain for what you're doing.
You don't want to leave your
house, your home and your land.
I know it is a heavy burden
on you. I know this very well.
The houses are not
important, Osman Bey.
Our blood is mixed with this
land and we leave it now.
We sacrificed many of our
sons and daughters for Sogut.
I pray to Allah that you have a plan.
We knew you as a different
man. You never do such a thing.
Now I know...
I know you are upset with me.
But you should also know this.
I've done only the thing I need to do.
Farewell now.
Farewell.
We'll get it all back, my Bey.
They don't know the truth.
The devilish woman, who
did all this to us and Lukas.
I'll make them pay in a way
no one has ever seen before.
I'll take the revenge of Sogut
and all the people cried...
...in such a way that...
I swear it.
You said you were going to save our son.
I have no one to trust but you, Bayhan Bey.
-You'll save him, right?
-We'll save him.
Our son will be with you
safe and sound today.
Hazal Hatun.
I know we don't like each other at all.
But we got the same wound.
You should know that I add Saruca
And Fatma to my prayers for Yusuf.
Oh, Black Widow!
Excuse me, please. It's
because of the pain I have.
Begum Hatun.
May Allah protect our children.
Ameen.
I also pray for your brother.
Thank you.
It's time to be united now.
Open the gates!
Commander Lukas sent us. He got the news!
Osman will kidnap the prisoners!
We'll secure the castle! Come on!
This is the last order of Commander Lukas.
Gates will not be opened until his arrival!
If you don't open the gates,
you'll pay for it with your lives!
They will save the
prisoners! Didn't you hear us!?
Even if you are Commander Lucas'
soldier, these gates won't open!
Oh Allah. What are we going to do now?
One way or another, those gates will be opened.
Come quickly!
The prisoners escaped! They killed the soldiers!
Oh Allah, help us.
Soldiers! What we said came true!
Open the gates, or the prisoners will escape!
Don't you hear us!
Come on!
If the prisoners escape, you
will be responsible for this!
Open the gates!
That's better.
Hold on sister, we are coming.
Come on.
The prisoners are running away! Spread out!
Brother?
Fatma..
You, stop.
Remove your helmet.
I am telling you, remove your helmet!
Boran.
Shields!
Come on!
Fire!
The Righteous!
Shields!
-Allah is the Greatest!
The Righteous!
-Allah is eternal!
-Allah is right!
Allah is the Greatest!
Which dastard hit me?
Which of you dastards beat me in the prison!?
Come here, you dog!
You dastards!
Allah is the Greatest!
Alps, bring the horses!
Open the gates! Come on alps!
-My shahzade!
-Shields!
Shields!
Brother!
-Brother, are you okay?
Brother are you okay?
Brother?
This arrow could pierce even the
toughest armor. How is this possible?
This will protect you.
It'll give you strength.
I have my strength here.
We didn't try that brother.
Thank Allah!
Are you okay sister?
I'm okay brother.
Yusuf, Saruca. Are you okay?
-We're okay my Bey.
-We're okay.
Allah!
-Let's leave now.
-Come on!
Come on! Back on the horses!
Come on.
Turahan.
Did you hide it all?
Yes my Bey.
The infidels won't sense anything.
Open up then.
What else?
Thank you.
Turahan.
My Bey.
No one will follow us
except for you and two Alps.
Alps will go outside the city.
As you wish my Bey.
Come on Alps. Let's leave.
If your plan succeeds, my Bey...
...the infidels can never take Turk's land.
The infidels will see...
...and the people will see the truth Bala.
My Bey. Gencer Bey's here to see you.
Let him in.
Come on in Gencer Bey.
Come in.
Know that I didn't put my hand under the rock...
...I put my whole body under there.
But, Osman didn't lose his arrogance...
....and hold the hand I offered him.
Sogut...
...will be given to infidels.
This is defying the tore, Karesi Bey.
Osman Bey accused me
of failing to protect my land.
Okay.
But I'll die before I let the infidels...
...have a piece of our land.
Of course not.
You are an honorable man.
That's why I'm telling you...
...you don't belong with Osman anymore.
What do you mean Karesi Bey?
Listen to me well.
These are Osman's last moments.
Come and swear loyalty to me.
Join my side...
...and I'll make you rich.
I swear loyalty to the one that
makes others lower their heads...
...not to the one that lower their own head.
They didn't know we would come here.
-My bey...
-If not...
...they wouldn't be sitting
around a fire like this.
Get out of my sight now.
Gencer Bey, don't ever make
a mistake like this ever again.
I asked you to show us a
way out but what did you do?
You talk about Karesi
who works with the infidels.
Like that's not enough, you talk over my rule.
My bey.
Enough Gencer Bey.
They're coming.
Osman emptied out Sogut as he promised.
And we brought the captives as we promised.
Let's see...
...who is going to be the winner today Lucas.
Let them come.
Let them...
Let them come to Sogut where
their dreams will be shattered.
Fatma.
According to the agreement...
...there is no alp or folk left in Sogut.
Now...
Now, you should keep your promise too.
Bring Fatma and the boys.
What do you think Lucas?
Should we end Osman and Bala Hatun's misery now?
Since he kept his promise...
Bring the captives.
Fatma
Fatma. Fatma.
So, this is your move, huh?
Who do you think you are kidding, Osman?
We know that you planted
gunpowder everywhere in Sogut.
So you were going to destroy the city
on us, after you got your daughter, huh?
Know that if there is one spark...
...Fatma Hatun will die.
You heard us, Osman. Give
the order to your soldiers.
Sogut will be cleared of
gunpowder immediately...
...and it will be surrendered
to us as we agreed.
Who...
...led you into this, huh?
Whose trap have you fallen into?
There is no gunpowder in Sogut.
I am about to run out of patience, Osman.
Stop lying and surrender the city immediately.
If my scout outside can't
get the news from me...
...your daughter, Fatma, will die.
You say so, huh?
Mother! Father!
How can it be, Lukas?
Fatma.
Daughter!
Thank Allah!
-Are you fine?
-I'm fine, mother. I'm fine.
Father!
Osman is not going to blow up
his family together with us, right?
Soldiers!
Alps!
It's impossible!
I told you there's no Greek Fire in Sogut.
Bayhan Bey.
Begum Hatun.
...trusted my word.
You were tricked by me.
Once we left the headquarters,
Lucas' men dressed
in an alp's clothes gave
us the same letter, my bey.
They expect us to betray you for our loved ones.
Orhan and Alaeddin.
They're going to save them
from that castle tomorrow.
Bayhan Bey.
You'll do as the infidels want.
You will tell them about our plans but...
...you'll give them as much
information as we want.
Bayhan Bey told you...
...only the parts I wanted you to know.
I'll kill you with your son, Bayhan.
Damn it.
We are trapped here, Lukas.
Wait there.
Alps!
Closed the gates.
Everyone will see what happens to those
setting their eyes on the lands of Turks.
You'll taste this sharpened sword.
Today...
...so much blood will be shed.
So much!